[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
HWANG DAESIK
-[sighs] -[Hwang] For crying out loud.
Not a single one of those so-called government ministers ever comes prepared.
I swear.
They should have everything ready before I even say a word.
Advisor Jang, what brings you here at the crack of dawn?
General, you're attending the ten o'clock meeting today, right?
Yeah. [coughs] Oh, God.
[sniffles] I don't know if it's the season,
but I feel like crap. [coughs]
[sniffles] So, um, what about the meeting?
Well, since you're a little under the weather,
why don't you take break on this one?
What? You think I should cancel it?
Oh, no. Today's meeting…
must start on schedule.
At 10:00 a.m. sharp.
Is this C-4?
-[agents chattering] -[typewriter keys clacking]
-[Geonyoung] Miss Oh. -Yes?
Has Captain Min Jonghwan come in yet?
No, haven't seen him today.
Miss Oh.
I'm gonna tell you something very important.
Listen carefully.
Min is gonna have…
a bomb with him today.
A… A bomb? Really?
Min has arrived for the meeting.
Let's move, then.
Miss Oh.
Let's keep this strictly between the two of us…
until we've apprehended Baek Kitae.
Do you know where General Hwang is?
[soldier] Present arms!
[soldiers] Yes, sir!
HWANG DAESIK
Min just arrived in the office.
What about Colonel Baek?
I didn't see him around earlier.
[Kang] Are you looking for something, ma'am?
Where are you going?
[humming] Captain Min.
Captain, hey.
Ah. Yes, sir.
So, did you manage to get what I asked you for?
Oh, yes, sir. I have it here.
PERSONAL RECORD
Thank you. New briefcase, huh?
Uh, yeah. Someone gave it to me.
[supervisor chuckling] Oh, nice. American-made.
How 'bout that. Made in the USA.
-How do you open this thing? -Uh, sorry.
I have a meeting soon. [chuckles]
Excuse me.
Have a good day, sir.
[Geonyoung] Captain Min.
Yes, sir.
You gonna grab a seat?
I was gonna have a smoke before the meeting.
All right.
[Kihun] When you're ready,
set the combination lock on the left side of the briefcase
to three, eight, six.
Once you do, the circuit will activate,
and it will automatically arm the detonator connected to the lock.
After exactly ten minutes, the bomb will go off.
The lethal blast radius is about 20 meters,
so leave it by your seat and get out of there.
-[general] Colonel Ahn. -Yes, sir.
[general] From now on, let's schedule these in the afternoon.
I haven't even had breakfast yet.
[Jaeho] Understood, sir.
[general] Where's the commander?
Don't worry, he's coming.
[Geonyoung] Captain Min.
Yes, sir?
The meeting is gonna start soon.
Where are you going?
Um, I was going to go get the report.
-[Min grunts] -[Jaeho] Stop! Don't move, you bastard!
[Jaeho] Everyone, stay where you are.
Colonel Ahn.
Get everybody out.
[officer 1] Are we evacuating?
Everybody needs to leave the room now! It's an emergency. Get out!
-Get out of here now. -[officer 2] What the hell is going on?
I'll explain later, sir. Hey, make sure the Chief of Staff gets out. Hurry!
-Move it, let's go! -[officer 3] Come on, hurry.
[Jaeho] Get him out of here now!
-Move it! -[officer 4] Hey…
-[Jaeho] Geez. -[officers chattering]
You too, Ahn.
Yeah.
And you, Miss Oh.
Let's go, asshole.
Come on.
Get out.
I'm not seeing a red wire.
You said he was supposed to be in this car!
Sir. Wait.
-Sir! We've got JIH vehicles incoming. -Kihyun.
Director Baek, it's a trap, sir.
-We have to go right now. -Kihyun.
What are you doing here? Come on, Kihyun.
-Stop, wait. Kihyun! -We have to go.
Kihyun, you're all right. Hey, Kihyun. Get off me, asshole.
-Hey, Kihyun! Wake up! -[Kihun] Sir, we have to go.
-[Kihun] We have to go. -Kihyun, wake up! Kihyun!
Wake up!
-Kihyun! Wake up, damn it! -[Kihun] Keep moving.
-Hey, cover him! -[Kitae] Kiyhun! Kihyun, please!
[Kihun] They're coming. Sir, we have to go now.
-Sir, please. -Wake up, for God's sake!
-Get the hell off me! Kihyun! -[Kihun] Cover him, you idiots! Hey!
-Get in the car, sir. Shut the door. -Kihyun, no!
You little rat.
Damn you.
[breathing heavily] Oh. Oh.
Oh, shit. I'm so screwed.
General.
Did you get him? Baek Kitae?
He escaped.
It'd be a lot better for us…
if that asshole was just dead.
Long as he's breathing, he's a liability.
Yes, sir. Copy that.
Goddamn.
If Jang hadn't told me,
I would've wound up dead, right?
Baek Kitae, that bastard. I don't believe it!
All right. I'm gonna…
I'm gonna head over to the safe house for now.
Stay put and make sure everything's okay.
-Got it? -[Jaeho] I'll get the car ready, sir.
-[Hwang] Yeah, let's go. -Hang on, wait a minute.
What?
I think that Baek Kihyun should be sent there before you.
Baek Kihyun?
Him first?
Trust me on this, General.
Baek Kitae's dangled bait in front of me before.
And if you decide to take it, you'll end up caught.
What? B-Bait?
Yes.
So what if this bomb is some kind of bait?
What do you mean, it's bait?
You think…
he'll ambush me on the way to the safe house?
Okay. So then…
Now what? What do you recommend?
I think you should just sit tight
and enjoy a nice, big bowl of jjajangmyeon, sir.
That's all you have to do.
[Hwang] What?
-Drop your head. -Yes, sir.
-[chopsticks clatter] -[huffs] Baek Kitae is a fucking bastard!
That sly little asshole is going down.
DIRECTOR BAEK KITAE
So Baek Kitae…
…made an attack on Hwang Daesik's armored car?
[sniffles] Yes, sir.
And Hwang was nowhere to be found, right?
-Correct, Mr. Pyo. -Just Baek Kihyun?
-Jang Geonyoung's pretty clever, huh? -[sniffles]
Everyone's plotting. No one's safe.
-[sniffles] -Someone's gonna have to die.
It's not gonna be me.
It better not be.
What is this?
Get him out.
-Go. It's fine. -[sniffles]
I was just going to call you.
What's going on with Baek Kitae?
Where do you think someone like him would hide?
You lost him?
The KCIA's got a few major safe houses, doesn't it?
I want a detailed map with all their locations marked right now.
Let's make a deal first.
Baek Kitae is captured…
and this chair is mine.
-Where are the safe hou-- -I want your word on this first.
Why don't I…
have these soldiers drag you down to the basement of the JIH
and we can talk there instead?
-You like that option better? -[sighs]
Come on, don't do this.
-The safe houses. -All right, all right.
Give me a sec.
The map's in my office.
[Geonyoung] Go with him.
Oh, look at you.
[gasps] My goodness. What happened, Chief Cheon?
Oh, gosh, you look awful right now.
I haven't heard from you for awhile. Guess you're a little busy.
So what brings you here today, Madam Shin?
Well, you'll be glad to know
that I've been praying day and night for you, sir.
You better be fucking kidding me with this praying shit.
Hwang is coming. He's out for blood, don't you get that?
Staring up at the sky and mumbling isn't gonna solve anything.
They kick the crap out of you and you're as blockheaded as ever.
You're such a helpless, pathetic man, but you can't stop running your mouth.
That certainly explains why you're still rotting in this dungeon.
Doesn't it?
Are you on drugs?
-What's the matter with you? -All right.
You listen here, Chief Cheon.
You're not the president's Chief of Staff anymore.
This is a completely different world now.
How can you possibly be this clueless?
Baek Kitae has a warrant out for his arrest.
I warned you, didn't I?
General Hwang isn't the kind of man who'll go down that easily.
That damn bald son of a bitch is practically invincible, I swear.
Oh, stop dwelling on those thoughts.
Do you wanna stay here forever?
Madam Shin,
is there any way for me to be released?
Perhaps.
It all depends on how you play this.
-This next part is crucial. -[door opens]
Well, look at you!
It's been a while, Chief Cheon.
Gosh, you've really been trying to knock my block off, haven't you?
You should be thanking Madam Shin right now.
You'd have a bullet in your skull if it weren't for this woman here,
you son of a bitch.
The truth is, I'm only here because of her, just so you know.
Anything you wanna share with me?
Just talk to him.
I went to a lot of trouble to arrange this meeting.
We need to work together to find a way to survive.
Don't you think?
Apparently he doesn't even wanna make it through the night.
[grunting] Oh, well.
-How about this? -[gun clicks]
We'll put you in a shallow grave alongside Baek Kitae…
The two of you together.
-You piece of garbage! -General Hwang.
What do you want from me, sir?
Bang, got ya! Bang, bang!
Now that's the attitude I'm looking for.
My fellow citizens, I'm Cheon Seokjung, Chief of Staff…
-[camera shutters clicking] -…to the president.
To begin, I'd like to express my genuine relief
that the truth has finally come to light.
I'd also like to address the slush fund ledger,
which has been reported on by many media outlets.
I'd like to be clear.
The aforementioned ledger was not mine.
It is the property of KCIA Director Baek Kitae and documents the scale…
of his elaborate criminal enterprise.
As the Joint Investigation Headquarters intensified its inquiry
and his crimes were on the verge of being exposed,
Acting Director Baek Kitae committed the grave crime
of plotting the assassination of General Hwang Daesik,
the head of the JIH and a prominent figure in government.
Fortunately, General Hwang uncovered this violent plot in advance
and marshaled a swift response,
foiling the attempt on his life before it could be carried out.
I need you to tell me something.
Why do the reports all say Cheon's money belongs to Baek Kitae?
I want Cheon close. He could be useful in the future.
He stepped down as Chief of Staff, so…
Let's wrap this up, all right?
You think I struggled for nine years,
surviving through hell on earth, just to crash and burn like this?
You know damn well Baek Kitae didn't plan all this on his own.
Cheon and Baek Kitae have to go down together to put a stop to this.
You better be careful.
I decide when and how we end this, Advisor Jang.
Come on, Hwang, wake up!
That's enough, sir. Calm down.
Lower your gun, shithead.
I said that's enough.
…if it weren't for you, Advisor Jang,
there's no doubt I'd be dead right now.
Baek Kitae thought he was so clever. Thought we'd never see him coming.
Sneaky bastard.
Hey.
You've done an excellent job up until now.
So I think
that you've earned yourself some rest.
What do you say?
I'll send Special Forces with you.
Find Baek and kill him before the day is over.
Yes, sir. I'll put an end to this.
Your time's finally up, Baek Kitae.
[anchor on TV] Breaking news.
The slush fund ledger previously believed to belong to Chief of Staff Cheon Seokjung
has now been definitively linked to Acting KCIA Director Baek Kitae.
Earlier this morning, as the investigation closed in on Baek,
sources say he suddenly disappeared.
Meanwhile, Chief of Staff Cheon Seokjung has stated that
he takes full political responsibility for the situation
and promptly announced his resignation.
Mr. Cheon also released a public statement
calling for a thorough criminal investigation
into Acting Director Baek Kitae, who has continued to evade authorities.
-[knocks on door] -[door opens]
Director Baek. I don't know how they found it,
but the JIH just raided the safe house in Segeomjeong.
[Seokjung] …foiling the attempt on his life before it could be carried out.
I can say with utmost certainty,
-these developments demonstrate… -[Kihun] Sir?
…the full extent of Baek Kitae's traitorous activities.
-His actions will no longer be concealed… -We can't stay here much longer.
And I would be remiss in my duties as a former government official…
Where do you wanna go?
…this great nation if I didn't take a moment
to express my deepest possible gratitude to General Hwang Daesik,
and call for a thorough and impartial investigation into Baek Kitae,
who has deceived the investigative authorities
and committed acts of heinous consequence.
[Yuji] So did you finish what you had to do?
[Kitae] I'm sorry.
What do you need from me?
Please send a boat for me when you can.
It's an emergency.
All right.
[Kitae] They're sending a boat to Busan.
We're headed to Busan then?
How's Kihyun?
Any information?
Not much, sir. Sorry.
It appears he was taken directly to the ER…
but that's as much as I've heard.
Just keep checking.
Of course, sir.
[Geonyoung] What have you got?
Well, my contact in Japan said Choi Yuji has already left town.
As you suspected he would, Baek Kitae is probably heading that way.
-[Geonyoung] And Cheon Seokjung? -[sighs]
He's nowhere to be found.
EXPORT IS THE CULMINATION OF NATIONAL POWER
Kitae.
Wha… What are you…
Look, I know.
I completely understand how you feel.
But I had no choice.
Hwang Daesik told me if I didn't obey, he'd murder me right then and there.
What was I supposed to do?
There are no other moves to make if you can't even ensure your survival.
If you'd taken care of Hwang Daesik, we'd be fine by now, Baek.
Just listen, all right?
At this point, this country's gonna end up
in the hands of those Army Neanderthals.
We can't be turning on each other right now.
If I survive, then you survive.
And so does your family.
Hwang and I talked, and we made a deal.
Do some jail time, just a quick little stint,
and when you come back out…
we pick up where we left off with our business.
Just trust me one more time and we're home free.
I'm pretty much the only person you can trust right now!
What?
You think I won't ever get this seat?
Believe me.
[shouting] Before I die…
you're gonna see that you're wrong about that.
You deserve to sit here as well.
I've always said that, right?
After me, it's you.
Kitae.
We have more cards left in the deck.
What happened to trust?
Have you ever trusted me?
That's what I thought.
Ugh, goddamn it.
Where were you? I-I, uh…
I was just trying to clear things out.
50, 71, 16.
Open it.
What's the combo?
Shit, it's hot. [winces]
Seventy-one.
-Sixteen. -Sixteen.
This is everything? [chuckles]
What's wrong? Not enough?
I just expected a lot more than this.
Oh, shit.
[chuckling] Where did I leave it now?
Give me a break, man.
Well…
After you failed to take out Hwang,
they turned off the power here.
Turned off all utilities.
Water, too.
Shame, isn't it? [sighs]
You did all the hard work, and someone else got rich.
Cheon Seokjung took it for himself and hung you out to dry.
Kitae.
You and I… are humble servants.
Government lackeys. Right?
We just try our best to do what we're told.
We're both resigned to that fate.
Come on, how much power do we have?
Is that why you jumped into bed with Jang again, you bald little rat?
It's not what you think, okay?
I'll explain it.
Just listen…
Kitae.
Don't do this.
I'll do anything you want.
I swear!
I won't ever betray you again.
I'll help you get everything you ever wanted!
I swear to God.
Kitae.
Kitae!
Listen.
I told Jang everything. It's all true, okay?
You're right, I told him everything. Happy now?
I know you murdered Director General Hwang and took his seat.
So, hey.
How are we different, huh?
Huh?
Why am I the one who has to die?
[shouting] Why me? Huh? Why?
Why am I the only one?
Hey! Why am I the one who has to die?
The boat should be arriving in three hours, sir.
We need to leave for Busan right away.
And Kihyun?
Well, sir…
Tell me.
Apparently he's in bad shape.
Baek Kihyun. How is he?
They said…
he might not make it much longer.
SEONGSAN HOSPITAL
208 - BAEK KIHYUN
-[gunshots continue] -[people clamoring]
-[explosion] -[soldiers exclaim]
-[breathing heavily] -[soldiers groaning]
-[gasps] -[gunshot]
You still think you're in the right?
Are you that stupid and naive?
You think by taking me down, you're changing the world?
I guess you still don't get it.
The world has already changed.
And the thing is…
there isn't a place for you in it.
You're finished.
What about you?
Where do you fit?
[Kitae] I was…
serving my country.
Everything I did…
I did for the sake of this nation.
-[gasps] -Mommy?
Are you okay?
[exhales] Here, sweetie.
[exhales] I'm okay.
Mommy's okay.
Everything's okay.
[Hwang] All I can say is, "Good riddance."
-[laughing] -[laughter]
Ah, look who it is.
So, are you leaving town?
Thanks for your hard work.
Where's the 70 billion?
Where'd you put all that money?
Uh-oh, here we go.
I told you, it's going right into the country's treasury.
Can you believe this?
[sighs] Ah, man, look at this guy.
-All right, Colonel Ahn. Got it? -Yes, sir.
Geez, what a mess, huh?
And what's this?
A token of my gratitude.
Shame to watch you walk around in that shabby wardrobe
for the rest of your life.
You're a man who's supposed to be serving his country, after all.
If you're gonna become a high-power prosecutor
or a bigwig attorney,
you'll need one good suit, won't you? [chuckles]
[sighing] Oh, gosh. Well…
You going back?
To Busan, I mean?
Yes.
And what about you? What's your next move?
Excuse me, Colonel Baek?
You have any regrets?
You have to kill Baek Kitae.
That's the only way you'll survive this now.
And the same goes for your sister and your little niece.
It's the only way they'll live.
[Geonyoung] I remember saying something a while back to Baek Kitae.
Something like…
"Claiming you acted the way you did because the world is crazy
is nothing more than a flimsy excuse."
At the end of the day,
everyone makes their own choices in this life.
As for me?
In order to bring him down,
I sold out.
I gave up my own sense of duty and patriotism to the men in power.
Baek Kitae and I…
both betrayed our values.
And what was it all really for?
-[President Park] My friend. -[Kitae] Yes, sir.
Keep a close watch on Cho and report to me regularly.
Of course, sir.
I think it's time to go in, Madam Shin.
'Cause I'm getting impatient.
All right, let's go.
[whispers] So, I'll be the director?
My friend.